pagelines.com 2015-09-05

# Privacy Policy - PageLines

**What information do we collect?**

Like most website operators, we collect non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, the date and time of each visitor request, and the duration of use. Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use our websites and services, and to optimize our websites and services.

We also collect potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our websites. We only disclose logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that we use and disclose personally-identifying information as described below.

Certain visitors to our websites choose to interact with us in ways that require us to gather additional personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that we gather depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who register on our websites to provide a username and email address. Those who purchase any of our services are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, we collect such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with us. We do not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

We may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to our websites. However, we do not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one or more of the following ways:

• To improve our websites  
• To improve customer service  
• To process transactions  
• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature  
• To send periodic emails

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

In addition, we may use non-personally identifiable information for marketing or advertising purposes.

**How do we protect your information?**

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied financial or other sensitive information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database, where it is accessible only to those who are authorized with special access rights to such systems and who are required to keep the information confidential.

After a purchase transaction, your financial information is not kept on file by us for more than 60 days.

**To whom do we disclose your information?**

We disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of our employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf or to provide services available at our websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using our websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties any personally-identifiable information.

Other than to our employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, we disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when we believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect our property or rights, or the property or rights of third parties or the public at large.

We may provide non-personally identifiable information to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of our websites, and their website access preferences. Visitors to our websites who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our websites, with the caveat that certain features of our websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies..

**Business Transfers**

If we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), and we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
